Frederick Loewe Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Photographs (Box 11)
  - Snapshots, many with FL, various locales (65) (Box-folder 11/15)
  - Snapshots, many with FL, various locales (65) (Box-folder 11/16)
  - Snapshots, FL and Palms Springs home (72) (Box-folder 11/17)
  - Snapshots, FL and Palms Springs home (210) (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Snapshots, last known photos of FL (33) with negatives (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Palm Springs home exterior, 8"x10" in color (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Aerial photos (2) (Box-folder 11/21)
  - Slides of exterior (2) (Box-folder 11/22)
- Business Papers (Box 12-13)
  - Appraisal of manuscript score of My fair lady, 1965 Apr. 23, Bound typescript; [5] p.; Laid in: correspondence with Library of Congress; [5] p. (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Draft of affidavit of Frederick Loewe re Greater Palm Springs Development Co., 1965 Oct. 21, Typescript; 33 p. (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Tamarisk Country Club correspondence, 1966, 3 items; [4] p. (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Deposition of Frederick Loewe, 1969 Apr. 25, Bound typescript; [108] p.; Laid in: notes; [8] p. (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Agreements with Franklin Mint Corporation, 1984 Mar. 30 and July 3, [5] p. each (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Camelot tour schedule, 1986, Typescript; [2] p. (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Copy codicil of Frederick Loewe (will), 1986 June 19, Bound typescript; [4] p. (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Copy codicil of Frederick Loewe (will), 1987 Oct. 5, Typescript; [4] p. (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Appraisal report of the Loewe estate, 1988 Apr. 27, Bound typescript, photographs; approximately [100] p. (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Deductible Charities
    - Desert Hospital
      - Instrument of irrevocable gift, 1969 Dec. 15 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Correspondence, notes, brochures, 1965-1986, undated, 61 items (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Eisenhower Medical Center
      - Instrument of irrevocable gift, 1969 Dec. 15 (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1971, 9 items (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Palm Springs Desert Museum
      - Correspondence, 1969-1976, 6 items (Box-folder 12/12)
    - University of Redlands
      - Correspondence, 1966-1975, 6 items (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Correspondence and other papers, 1964-1985, undated, 62 items (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Appraisals/valuations of portfolio, 1981-1987, Correspondence and reports, 113 items (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Contracts, bills, proposals re house modeling, 1963, 29 items (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Correspondence with attorney Benjamin Aslan, 1965-1987, 17 items (Box-folder 13/2)